Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Alone as a blade♪
♪وحيدًا كالسيف♪
♪Charging into the storm♪
♪الاندفاع نحو العاصفة♪
♪Fate brings us face to face♪
♪القدر يجمعنا وجهاً لوجه♪
♪We play this game as opponents♪
♪نحن نلعب هذه اللعبة كخصوم♪
♪Blades may clash yet find their peace♪
♪قد تتصادم الشفرات ولكنها تجد السلام ♪
♪But this deadly game won't cease♪
♪ولكن هذه اللعبة القاتلة لن تتوقف♪
♪One inch more, my bones shatter♪
♪بوصة واحدة أخرى، عظامي تتحطم♪
♪Burdens♪
♪الأعباء♪
♪Lead to diverging paths♪
♪تؤدي إلى مسارات متباينة♪
♪Love becomes a sin♪
♪الحب يصبح خطيئة♪
♪Endless schemes♪
♪مخططات لا نهاية لها♪
♪You and I stand divided♪
♪أنت وأنا نقف منقسمين♪
♪The desire♪
♪الرغبة♪
♪Burns down the past♪
♪يحرق الماضي♪
♪When there is no retreat♪
♪عندما لا يكون هناك تراجع♪
♪How do we rewrite our fate♪
♪كيف نعيد كتابة مصيرنا♪
=Moonlit Order=
=أمر مقمر=
=Episode 1=
=الحلقة 1=
Hyah!
هيا!
(Feng Zuoren, Xue Guardian Commander)
(فنغ زورين، قائد حارس شيويه)
(Emperor Jia, Emperor of the Hua Dynasty)
(الإمبراطور جيا، إمبراطور أسرة هوا)
The Xue Guardians have eliminated the traitors.
لقد قام حراس شيو بالقضاء على الخونة.
Commander Feng Zuoren, heed the command.
القائد فنغ زورين، استمع للأمر.
I command you
انا آمرك
to marry into the Xue family of Lord Dingyuan.
للزواج من عائلة شيويه للسيد دينغيوان.
Jia Xun is definitely hiding there.
من المؤكد أن جيا شون يختبئ هناك.
You must find him before others do
يجب عليك أن تجده قبل أن يفعل الآخرون ذلك
and bring me his head.
وأحضر لي رأسه.
I will locate the remnants
سأحدد البقايا
and eradicate them
والقضاء عليهم
to protect our nation.
لحماية أمتنا.
Get up.
استيقظ.
It's a crucial matter.
إنها مسألة حاسمة.
Do not
لا
be exposed.
تكون معرضة للخطر.
Understood.
مفهومة.
(His Majesty has been in poor health.)
(لقد كان جلالته في حالة صحية سيئة.)
(The prince is still young.)
(الأمير لا يزال شابا.)
(The nation)
(الأمة)
(hangs in precarious balance.)
(يعلق في توازن محفوف بالمخاطر.)
(Years ago,)
(منذ سنوات)
(His Majesty's brother Jia Xun was the Crown Prince.)
(كان شقيق جلالته جيا شون ولي العهد.)
(Exiled among commoners,)
(منفي بين عامة الناس)
(he has turned twenty this year.)
(لقد بلغ العشرين من عمره هذا العام.)
(We implore Your Majesty)
(نرجو من جلالتكم)
(to reclaim Jia Xun and restore his royal status)
(لاستعادة جيا شون واستعادة مكانته الملكية)
(to stabilize the court.)
(لتثبيت المحكمة.)
(Xue's Textile) A new textile shop
(Xue's Textile) متجر نسيج جديد
opened on Xue Street?
افتتح في شارع شيويه؟
What a pretty lady.
كم هي جميلة هذه السيدة.
Don't tell me she's the shopkeeper.
لا تخبرني أنها صاحبة المتجر.
Are you the shopkeeper?
هل أنت صاحب المتجر؟
Where can I get this fabric?
أين يمكنني الحصول على هذا القماش؟
It looks amazing.
إنه يبدو مذهلا.
We have new stock.
لدينا مخزون جديد.
Come see inside.
تعال وانظر إلى الداخل.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Zhang Er'gou.
تشانغ إرجو.
Get your filthy hands off her.
أبعد يديك القذرة عنها.
(Xue Hexu, Second Son of the Xue Family)
(شيويه هيكسو، الابن الثاني لعائلة شيويه)
Xue Hexu.
شيويه هيكسو.
You again?
انت مرة اخرى؟
What an epic entrance.
يا له من مدخل ملحمي!
Collect your rent
تحصيل الإيجار الخاص بك
and stay out of this.
والبقاء خارج هذا.
You punk.
أنت بانك.
Don't you know who runs this place?
ألا تعرف من يدير هذا المكان؟
Harassing the shopkeeper
مضايقة صاحب المتجر
means opposing the Xue family.
يعني معارضة عائلة شيويه.
Don't forget
لا تنسى
that your mother rents our butcher stall.
أن والدتك تستأجر محل الجزارة لدينا.
That's your family's only livelihood.
هذا هو مصدر رزق عائلتك الوحيد.
Now get lost.
الآن ابتعد.
Thank you for helping, young master.
شكرا لمساعدتك يا سيدي الشاب.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Since you rent from us for business,
نظرًا لأنك تستأجر منا لأغراض العمل،
it's our duty
إنه واجبنا
to protect you.
لحمايتك.
Here's six months' rent.
وهنا إيجار ستة أشهر.
So prompt with the rent payments.
سريع جدًا في دفع الإيجار.
But with such sparse business,
ولكن مع مثل هذه الأعمال المتناثرة،
where does the money come from?
من أين تأتي الأموال؟
It's even newly minted.
حتى أنها جديدة تماما.
If I hadn't intervened,
لو لم أتدخل،
Zhang Er'gou
تشانغ إرجو
would've died by now, right?
لقد كنت سأموت الآن، أليس كذلك؟
Does anyone want
هل يريد أحد
a rent reduction?
تخفيض الإيجار؟
Mr. Xue.
السيد شيويه.
You mean it?
هل تقصد ذلك؟
My family and I always keep our word.
أنا وعائلتي نلتزم دائمًا بكلمتنا.
But there's no free lunch from you.
ولكن لا يوجد غداء مجاني منك.
What do you want in exchange?
ماذا تريد في المقابل؟
We know your methods
نحن نعرف أساليبك
all too well.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
Nonsense.
هراء.
This lady is trying
هذه السيدة تحاول
to make a living alone.
لكسب لقمة العيش بمفردي.
A nearby neighbor is better than a distant family.
الجار القريب خير من عائلة بعيدة.
You will
سوف تفعلها
keep her protected.
احفظها محمية.
Keep watch on her shop
راقب متجرها
for any suspicious activity.
لأي نشاط مشبوه.
Keep me updated.
أبقيني على اطلاع.
Useful leads get you
مصادر مفيدة تحصل عليها
10% off on the rent
خصم 10% على الإيجار
starting next month.
ابتداء من الشهر المقبل.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I guarantee
انا اضمن
not even a fly will get through.
حتى الذبابة لن تمر.
Madam.
سيدتي.
You'd better
من الأفضل لك
not cause trouble on our turf.
لا تسبب مشاكل في ملعبنا.
If you're looking for trouble,
إذا كنت تبحث عن المتاعب،
pack up and leave.
حزم أمتعتك وغادر.
(Once I marry into your family,)
(بمجرد أن أتزوج من عائلتك)
(the first person I kill)
(أول شخص أقتله)
(will be you.)
(سوف تكون انت.)
Mr. Xue.
السيد شيويه.
Something happened.
لقد حدث شيء ما.
(Xue Mansion)
(قصر شيويه)
(Xue Fugui, Lord Dingyuan)
(شيويه فوجوي، اللورد دينغيوان)
His Majesty assigned you a bride?
هل خصص لك جلالته عروسة؟
His Majesty fell for the rumors
لقد صدق جلالته الشائعات
and believes that
ويعتقد أن
we're hiding the former Crown Prince Jia Xun.
نحن نخفي ولي العهد السابق جيا شون.
He assigned me a new wife to investigate
لقد عيّن لي زوجة جديدة للتحقيق
and spy on us.
وتجسس علينا.
The former Crown Prince disappeared years ago.
اختفى ولي العهد السابق منذ سنوات.
Why bring it up now?
لماذا طرح هذا الموضوع الآن؟
His Majesty is gravely ill.
جلالته مريض بشكل خطير.
His only son is too young to inherit the throne.
ابنه الوحيد صغير جدًا على وراثة العرش.
He must be recalling his own usurpation of power
لا بد أنه يتذكر اغتصابه للسلطة
and fearing that Jia Xun might return to claim the throne.
وخوفا من أن جيا شون قد يعود للمطالبة بالعرش.
Such battles
مثل هذه المعارك
always bring bloodshed.
يؤدي دائما إلى سفك الدماء.
Those in power never consider the people's welfare.
إن أصحاب السلطة لا يفكرون مطلقا في مصلحة الشعب.
With His Majesty's paranoia,
مع جنون جلالته،
he'd rather slaughter innocents than take risks.
يفضل ذبح الأبرياء بدلاً من المخاطرة.
Our family stands on the brink of disaster.
عائلتنا تقف على شفا الكارثة.
Don't tell your grandmother yet.
لا تخبر جدتك بعد
If that new bride makes any suspicious move...
إذا قامت تلك العروس الجديدة بأية حركة مشبوهة...
I'll kill her.
سأقتلها
Father,
أب،
I won't let anyone harm the Xue family.
لن أسمح لأحد أن يؤذي عائلة شيو.
You're ruthless toward outsiders.
أنت قاسي تجاه الغرباء.
Perhaps
ربما
it's good for you.
إنه جيد لك.
(Grand Tutor's Mansion)
(قصر المعلم الأعظم)
This is madness.
هذا جنون.
They brought up the former Crown Prince
لقد أحضروا ولي العهد السابق
(Grand Tutor Zhou, Top Grand Tutor) to force His Majesty's
(المعلم الأعظم تشو، المعلم الأعظم الأعلى) لإجبار جلالته
abdication in his sickbed.
تنازل عن العرش وهو على فراش مرضه.
Let's kill them
دعونا نقتلهم
as a warning to others.
كتحذير للآخرين.
Someone might have beaten you to it.
ربما سبقك شخص ما إلى ذلك.
Chief Gu Qianfu of Jing'an Bureau.
الرئيس قو تشيان فو من مكتب جينغان.
Go to Lord Dingyuan's mansion.
اذهب إلى قصر اللورد دينغيوان.
Find the former Crown Prince.
العثور على ولي العهد السابق.
And execute him
وأعدموه
as a warning to others.
كتحذير للآخرين.
Wait. Don't kill him.
انتظر. لا تقتله.
Bring him to me alive.
أحضروه لي حياً.
I will bring him to you.
سأحضره إليك.
You shall execute him
سوف تقوم بإعدامه
as a warning to others.
كتحذير للآخرين.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Nowadays, His Majesty depends heavily
في الوقت الحاضر، يعتمد جلالته بشكل كبير
on the Xue Guardians
على حراس شيويه
and forgets the Jing'an Bureau.
وينسى مكتب جينغان.
We must not lose to them.
لا يجب علينا أن نخسر أمامهم.
Gu Qianfu.
قو تشيانفو.
As the backbone of the Jing'an Bureau,
باعتبارها العمود الفقري لمكتب جينجان،
you must outperform the Xue Guardians.
يجب عليك التفوق على حراس شيو.
I'll kill them.
سأقتلهم
Get to work.
اذهب إلى العمل.
(His Majesty's schemes run deep.)
(إن مخططات جلالته عميقة للغاية.)
(You think)
(كنت أعتقد)
(this can secure the throne for your young son?)
(هذا يمكن أن يؤمن العرش لابنك الصغير؟)
(Once I identify the real former Crown Prince,)
(بمجرد أن أتمكن من التعرف على ولي العهد السابق الحقيقي)
(this empire)
(هذه الإمبراطورية)
(will be mine.)
(سوف تكون لي.)
(Xue Mansion)
(قصر شيويه)
(Xue Street)
(شارع شيويه)
His Majesty sends a new bride to our family.
جلالته يرسل عروسة جديدة لعائلتنا.
(Liu Jiaoqian, Xue Dongfang's wife) What should
(ليو جياوتشيان، زوجة شيويه دونغ فانغ) ماذا ينبغي
Dongyang and I do if she bears children?
دونغيانغ وأنا أفعل إذا أنجبت أطفالاً؟
Besides, I heard Ms. Wang is a military hero
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، سمعت أن السيدة وانغ بطلة عسكرية
who just returned
الذي عاد للتو
from the border.
من الحدود.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
This wedding
هذا الزفاف
may help Father
قد يساعد الأب
recover from illness.
التعافي من المرض.
Don't lift the veil yet.
لا ترفع الحجاب بعد
The wedding isn't completed.
لم يكتمل الزفاف بعد.
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
I care little for such formalities.
أنا لا أهتم كثيرا بهذه الإجراءات الشكلية.
Mr. Xue.
السيد شيويه.
The textile shop is closed.
تم إغلاق محل النسيج.
The shopkeeper
صاحب المتجر
said she's getting married.
قالت أنها ستتزوج.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
She's right here.
إنها هنا.
So, you are Ms. Wang.
إذن، أنت السيدة وانغ.
You're acquainted?
هل تعرفت على بعض؟
My father gave me a textile shop
أعطاني والدي محلًا للنسيج
to experience commoners' lives.
لتجربة حياة عامة الناس.
But I'm bad at this.
ولكنني سيئة في هذا.
Please don't laugh at me.
من فضلك لا تضحك علي.
From now on, we'll be family.
من الآن فصاعدا، سوف نكون عائلة.
I could use your guidance on many things, Mr. Xue.
أستطيع الاستفادة من إرشاداتك في العديد من الأشياء، السيد شيويه.
He shouldn't be guiding you.
لا ينبغي له أن يرشدك.
You'll be our stepmother.
سوف تكوني زوجة أبينا.
It's you who should guide us.
أنت الذي يجب أن يرشدنا.
Hexu, greet our
هيكسو، تحية لنا
stepmother.
زوجة الأب.
Bad news.
اخبار سيئة.
Something went wrong.
لقد حدث خطأ ما.
(Xue Dongyang, First Son of the Xue Family)
(شيويه دونغيانغ، الابن الأول لعائلة شيويه)
Hurry.
عجل.
Our lord is dying.
ربنا يموت.
Father.
أب.
Father, are you okay?
أبي هل أنت بخير؟
(Who wanted to kill Lord Dingyuan?)
(من أراد قتل اللورد دينغيوان؟)
(Who did it?)
(من فعل ذلك؟)
Father. Father.
أب. أب.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
We just got married.
لقد تزوجنا للتو.
How am I supposed to live
كيف من المفترض أن أعيش؟
if anything happens to my lord?
إذا حدث أي شيء لسيدي؟
Dongyang, don't be scared.
دونغيانغ، لا تخف.
Have some candy.
خذ بعض الحلوى.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What did you see?
ماذا رأيت؟
Jiaoqian wouldn't let me have candies.
جياوتشيان لن يسمح لي بتناول الحلوى.
So I came looking for candies.
لذلك جئت أبحث عن الحلوى.
I saw Father wrestling someone for fun.
لقد رأيت الأب يصارع شخصًا ما من أجل المتعة.
I wanted to play, too.
أردت أن ألعب أيضاً.
Wrestling?
مصارعة؟
Father is ill.
الأب مريض.
How can he wrestle?
كيف يمكنه المصارعة؟
(Someone else was here?)
(هل كان هناك شخص آخر هنا؟)
(How reckless.)
(كم هو متهور.)
(The target is alerted.)
(تم تنبيه الهدف.)
Dongyang didn't know Father
دونغيانغ لم يعرف الأب
was under attack,
كان تحت الهجوم
and he made a commotion.
وأحدث ضجة.
The assassin got scared and escaped.
لقد خاف القاتل وهرب.
You saved Father.
لقد أنقذت أبي.
You're so brave.
أنت شجاع جدًا.
Let's report it.
دعونا نبلغ عن ذلك.
Ms. Wang.
السيدة وانغ.
I'm afraid you won't
أخشى أنك لن تفعل ذلك
be able to marry my father.
أن أكون قادراً على الزواج من والدي.
This is unfortunate.
هذا أمر مؤسف.
We're in trouble
نحن في ورطة
right on the day you came.
في اليوم الذي أتيت فيه.
Why don't you stay
لماذا لا تبقى؟
at home
في البيت
in case you get implicated?
في حال تورطك؟
(Xue Hexu.)
(شيويه هيكسو.)
(Second son of Xue Fugui.)
(الابن الثاني لشيويه فوجوي.)
(Household manager.)
(مدير المنزل.)
(Age 20.)
(العمر 20 عامًا)
(Target No.1.)
(الهدف رقم 1)
(Xue Dongyang.)
(شيويه دونغيانغ.)
(First son of Xue Fugui.)
(الابن الأول لـ Xue Fugui.)
(Husband of Liu Jiaoqian.)
(زوج ليو جياوتشيان.)
(Age 23.)
(العمر 23 عامًا)
(Target No.2.)
(الهدف رقم 2)
(Could be playing dumb.)
(قد يكون يلعب غبيًا.)
Pretty lady.
سيدة جميلة.
Dongyang, watch it.
دونغيانغ، شاهده.
(Xue Nuannuan.)
(شيويه نوانوان.)
(Daughter of Xue Fugui.)
(ابنة شيويه فوجوي.)
(Xue Nuannuan of Xue Family) (Twin sister of Xue Hexu.)
(Xue Nuannuan من عائلة Xue) (الأخت التوأم لـ Xue Hexu.)
(Age 20.)
(العمر 20 عامًا)
(Could be under disguise.)
(قد يكون متخفيًا.)
(Target No.3.)
(الهدف رقم 3)
(The former Crown Prince)
(ولي العهد السابق)
(could be anyone.)
(قد يكون أي شخص.)
(Kill them all so that he can't get away.)
(اقتلهم جميعا حتى لا يتمكن من الهرب.)
(Everyone is here.)
(الجميع هنا.)
(No outsiders.)
(لا يوجد غرباء.)
(It's time for them to perish.)
(لقد حان وقت هلاكهم.)
(You can't wait)
(لا يمكنك الانتظار)
(to make a move.)
(لإجراء تحرك.)
(Grandma, Xue Mansion)
(الجدة، قصر شيويه)
(She's in charge.)
(إنها المسؤولة.)
Madam.
سيدتي.
I am Lord Dingyuan's wife-to-be.
أنا زوجة اللورد دينغيوان المستقبلية.
I consider myself his wife,
أعتبر نفسي زوجته
although we haven't held the wedding.
على الرغم من أننا لم نقم حفل الزفاف.
How can I walk away
كيف يمكنني الابتعاد
when the lord is ill?
عندما يكون الرب مريضا؟
Good girl.
فتاة جيدة.
You're so devoted to my son.
أنت مخلص جدًا لإبني.
Fine.
بخير.
You sound devoted.
يبدو أنك مخلص.
I heard that the Yuechuan River is blessed by the river god.
سمعت أن نهر يوتشوان مبارك من قبل إله النهر.
We can offer you to the river god
يمكننا أن نقدم لك إله النهر
to restore health to my father.
لإعادة الصحة إلى والدي.
That's the least you could do for my father.
هذا أقل ما يمكنك فعله لوالدي.
Be sacrificed or leave.
تضحي أو اترك.
Ms. Wang.
السيدة وانغ.
Your choice.
اختيارك.
We are a family of military people.
نحن عائلة من العسكريين.
How can we send her to die?
كيف يمكننا أن نرسلها للموت؟
Hexu.
هيكسو.
We can't break the law.
لا يمكننا مخالفة القانون.
Mr. Xue.
السيد شيويه.
Since I'm married
منذ أن تزوجت
to your father,
إلى والدك
I can't leave when my husband
لا أستطيع المغادرة عندما يكون زوجي
is in trouble.
في ورطة.
Good girl.
فتاة جيدة.
Greet your stepmother.
سلم على زوجة أبيك.
I suggested that
لقد اقترحت ذلك
because Ms. Wang is devoted to Father.
لأن السيدة وانج مخلصة لأبيها.
Besides,
بجانب،
Father is badly ill,
الأب مريض بشدة
and she is loyal.
وهي مخلصة.
My suggestion makes sense.
اقتراحي منطقي.
Hexu.
هيكسو.
Why don't you sacrifice yourself?
لماذا لا تضحي بنفسك؟
She's married to your father.
إنها متزوجة من والدك.
That makes her our family.
وهذا يجعلها عائلتنا.
We should look after each other. That's what matters.
علينا أن نعتني ببعضنا البعض. هذا هو المهم.
You're so against her.
أنت ضدها تماما.
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
You don't want her to bear children and replace you
لا تريدها أن تنجب أطفالاً وتحل محلك
as the heir?
كالوريث؟
Don't be so petty.
لا تكن تافهاً هكذا.
(They look quite innocent.)
(يبدو أنهم أبرياء تمامًا.)
(But for His Majesty's reign,)
(ولكن لحكم جلالته)
(they must all die.)
(يجب أن يموتوا جميعا.)
You treat me so kindly.
لقد عاملتني بلطف شديد.
I don't know how to repay you.
لا أعرف كيف أرد لك الجميل.
Let me offer you tea
دعني أقدم لك الشاي
to express my gratitude.
لأعبر عن امتناني.
Madam.
سيدتي.
I'm thirsty. I'll drink first.
أنا عطشان. سأشرب أولاً.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Ungrateful brat.
طفل جاحد.
You shouldn't drink the tea
لا يجب عليك شرب الشاي
your stepmother offers to me.
زوجة أبيك تقدم لي عرضًا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I was wrong.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
This tea serves as my apology.
هذا الشاي بمثابة اعتذاري.
I offer this to you.
أعرض عليك هذا.
Stepmother.
زوجة الأب.
Please drink.
من فضلك اشرب.
Thank you for marrying my father.
شكرا لك على زواجك من والدي.
(This person is truly obstructive.)
(هذا الشخص معرقل حقا.)
You won't accept the tea.
لن تقبل الشاي.
Are you blaming me
هل تلومني؟
for offending you?
لإهانتك؟
Or perhaps,
أو ربما،
you're behind what happened today?
أنت وراء ما حدث اليوم؟
Assassins!
القتلة!
(Jing'an Bureau's daggers.)
(خناجر مكتب جينغان.)
(Grand Tutor Zhou.)
(المعلم الكبير تشو.)
(Why did he attack us?)
(لماذا هاجمنا؟)
(How dare you betray His Majesty?)
(كيف تجرؤ على خيانة جلالته؟)
Stay calm.
ابقى هادئا.
Follow our drills.
اتبع تدريباتنا.
Hide first.
إختبئ أولاً
I'll secure the hall.
سأقوم بتأمين القاعة.
(They're so fast!)
(إنهم سريعون جدًا!)
(Gu Qianfu, Chief of Jing'an Bureau)
(قو تشيان فو، رئيس مكتب جينغان)
Gu Qianfu.
قو تشيانفو.
Feng Zuoren.
فنغ زورين.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
You fools are courting death,
أيها الحمقى تتوددون إلى الموت،
coming to my turf.
قادم إلى أرضي.
I've always thought
لقد اعتقدت دائما
that you're a man.
أنك رجل.
Right.
يمين.
Are you a guy or a girl?
هل أنت رجل أم فتاة؟
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Trying to kill me again?
تحاول قتلي مرة أخرى؟
I know what you did.
انا أعلم ما فعلته.
You were about to exterminate
كنت على وشك الإبادة
the entire Xue family.
عائلة شيويه بأكملها.
Bone-Eroding Powder.
مسحوق تآكل العظام.
It erodes the bone marrow.
يؤدي إلى تآكل نخاع العظم.
You're doomed.
لقد حُكم عليك بالهلاك.
Thank goodness you're safe, Stepmother.
الحمد لله أنك بخير، زوجة الأب.
I was so worried.
لقد كنت قلقة للغاية.
You again?
انت مرة اخرى؟
I was worried about you.
لقد كنت قلقا عليك.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Petty trick.
خدعة تافهة.
I can kill your whole family.
أستطيع أن أقتل عائلتك بأكملها.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Why would a master like you
لماذا سيد مثلك
try to exterminate my entire family?
محاولة إبادة عائلتي بأكملها؟
Name your price.
حدد السعر الخاص بك.
I can pay you.
أستطيع أن أدفع لك.
Why do I want to kill you?
لماذا أريد قتلك؟
Are you really clueless?
هل أنت حقا لا تملك أدنى فكرة؟
I...
أنا...
I'm totally clueless.
أنا لا أعرف شيئا على الإطلاق.
You came in broad daylight.
لقد أتيت في وضح النهار.
Everybody has seen your face.
لقد رأى الجميع وجهك.
If my family dies on the same day,
إذا ماتت عائلتي في نفس اليوم،
where can you
أين يمكنك
possibly hide?
ربما تختبئ؟
The authorities will
وسوف تقوم السلطات
arrest you.
أعتقلك.
Are you suicidal?
هل انت تفكر في الانتحار؟
My single life
حياتي الفردية
for your entire clan's lives.
طوال حياة عشيرتك.
Fair trade.
معرض تجاري.
Is there no one
هل لا يوجد أحد
you care about in this world?
ما الذي تهتم به في هذا العالم؟
Those I cared about
الذين اهتممت بهم
all perished long ago.
لقد هلكوا جميعا منذ زمن طويل.
Bone-Eroding Powder, huh?
مسحوق تآكل العظام، أليس كذلك؟
Feng Zuoren.
فنغ زورين.
Gu Qianfu.
قو تشيانفو.
Got a death wish?
هل لديك رغبة في الموت؟
Not exactly.
ليس بالضبط.
Your palm strike
ضربة راحة يدك
combined our inner energies
جمعنا طاقاتنا الداخلية
and unblocked my Ren and Du meridians.
وقمت بإلغاء حظر خطوط الطول Ren و Du الخاصة بي.
The poison
السم
has been forced out.
لقد تم إجباره على الخروج.
Even so,
ومع ذلك،
your martial prowess is gone.
لقد ذهبت براعتك القتالية.
My inner energy.
طاقتي الداخلية.
I put Dispersing Powder on my chest.
أضع مسحوق التشتيت على صدري.
You got poisoned
لقد تم تسميمك
when you struck me.
عندما ضربتني.
Shameless.
وقح.
Everyone knows about the former Crown Prince.
الجميع يعرف عن ولي العهد السابق.
You barely married into the family
لقد تزوجت بالكاد في العائلة
and can't wait to hold a funeral.
ولا أستطيع الانتظار لإقامة جنازة.
Isn't this inappropriate?
أليس هذا غير مناسب؟
Why don't you work with me to find
لماذا لا تعمل معي للعثور على
the former Crown Prince?
ولي العهد السابق؟
Empty promises sound sweet.
الوعود الفارغة تبدو جميلة.
You simply
انت ببساطة
want to steal credit from us.
يريدون سرقة الفضل منا.
What's that smell?
ما هذه الرائحة؟
Despicable scum.
حثالة حقيرة.
♪You should've died by the blade♪
♪كان يجب أن تموت بالشفرة♪
♪Should've been trapped by me♪
♪كان ينبغي أن أحاصره♪
♪Yet deeper pain emerges♪
♪ولكن الألم الأعمق يظهر♪
♪Blurring hatred and love♪
♪خلط الكراهية والحب♪
♪I should've been the fatal blade♪
♪كان ينبغي أن أكون الشفرة القاتلة♪
♪Severing delusions and obsessions♪
♪التخلص من الأوهام والهواجس♪
♪Yet unintentionally, I disrupted the fate lines♪
♪ولكن دون قصد، قمت بتعطيل خطوط القدر♪
♪The deeper wild fantasies take root♪
♪تتجذر الخيالات البرية العميقة♪
♪The more the questions persist♪
♪كلما استمرت الأسئلة♪
♪Shouldn't have let my soul become so entangled♪
♪لا ينبغي أن أترك روحي تتشابك إلى هذا الحد♪
♪Yet fate plays its cruel game♪
♪ومع ذلك فإن القدر يلعب لعبته القاسية♪
♪Our resistance only deepens our love♪
♪مقاومتنا لا تزيد إلا من عمق حبنا♪
♪Not understanding your gaze, not grasping my hesitation♪
♪لا أفهم نظراتك، ولا أفهم ترددي♪
♪Can't confess true feelings♪
♪لا أستطيع الاعتراف بمشاعري الحقيقية♪
♪Partings and death come swiftly♪
♪الفراق والموت يأتيان بسرعة♪
♪All concealed in tear stains♪
♪كلها مخفية في بقع الدموع♪
♪You unknowingly bring chaos♪
♪أنت تجلب الفوضى دون علمك♪
♪Blades leave snow-like scars♪
♪الشفرات تترك ندوبًا تشبه الثلج♪
♪Treading moonlight with heavy steps♪
♪المشي على ضوء القمر بخطوات ثقيلة♪
♪Knocking at my heart's door♪
♪طرق باب قلبي♪
♪I shatter the mirrored self♪
♪أحطم الذات المرآة♪
♪Spring lingers in brows♪
♪الربيع يطول في الحواجب♪
♪Hide♪
♪إخفاء♪
♪Our resentment, reluctance, and weakness♪
♪استياءنا، وترددنا، وضعفنا♪
♪The deeper wild fantasies take root♪
♪تتجذر الخيالات البرية العميقة♪
♪The more the questions persist♪
♪كلما استمرت الأسئلة♪
♪Shouldn't have let my soul become so entangled♪
♪لا ينبغي أن أترك روحي تتشابك إلى هذا الحد♪
♪Yet fate plays its cruel game♪
♪ومع ذلك فإن القدر يلعب لعبته القاسية♪
♪Our resistance only deepens our love♪
♪مقاومتنا لا تزيد إلا من عمق حبنا♪
♪Your blazing gaze betrays matching fire within♪
♪نظرتك المشتعلة تكشف عن نار متطابقة في الداخل♪
♪Can't confess true feelings♪
♪لا أستطيع الاعتراف بمشاعري الحقيقية♪
♪Partings and death come swiftly♪
♪الفراق والموت يأتيان بسرعة♪
♪All concealed in tear stains♪
♪كلها مخفية في بقع الدموع♪